<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="student_one" model="student.student">
            <field name="name">Amal Chamlee</field>
            <field name="code">34AMCH</field>
            <field name="biography"> I am proud to be a Parkway Early Childhood Panda!!
I am from St. Louis, received a Bachelor's Degree in Education from the University of Dayton,
and my Masters in Education from Missouri Baptist University. I am certified to teach Early Childhood,
Early Childhood Special Education, and Elementary Education. This will be my seventh year at
Parkway Early Childhood after four years at Kirkwood Early Childhood Center in Early Childhood Special Education.
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="student_two" model="student.student">
            <field name="name">Bertie Leister</field>
            <field name="code">28BELT</field>
            <field name="biography">I am honored and humbled that I have been selected for
Teacher of the year at Lakeview Middle School. I earned my masters degree MAT in teaching majoring in
biology from the Citadel 1994. I attended undergrad at Charleston Southern University on a full athletic
scholarship and received a Bachelor Degree in Business Administration. I also attended Spartanburg
Methodist College on a full athletic scholarship and earned an associate’s degree. I am highly qualified in
both middle and high school science and earned my national board certification in 2012.
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="student_three" model="student.student">
            <field name="name">Drew Bell</field>
            <field name="code">16DRBL</field>
            <field name="biography">I am an Educator Effectiveness Strategist for the Madison Metropolitan
School District. In his role as a Strategist, he supports principals and assistant principals across elementary,
middle and high schools engage in the Educator Effectiveness System resulting in continuous improvement in
teaching and learning. Jorge’s background includes elementary assistant principal as well as teaching experience
at both elementary and middle levels.  Educational degrees include a Bachelor’s Degree in Elementary Education
from UW-Madison and a Master’s Degree in Educational Administration from Concordia University.
Jorge’s work is rooted in the belief that a great education is foundational to life success.
            </field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>